<root>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One of the dreams on my wish list is to spend more time in Thailand.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Slow travel now rivals the fly-to-Barcelona-for-lunch culture. Advocates savour the journey, travelling by train
      or boat or bicycle, or even on foot, rather than crammed into an airplane. They take time to plug into the local
      culture instead of racing through a list of tourist traps.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Sometimes I like to list the strongest arguments I can find to support a point of view I think is wrong. When I
      have them before me, I am up against a real opponent rather than a hypothetical one that is an easy target for me
      to hit.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      On its 2015 list, the Fish and Wildlife Service included the 'ea, or hawksbill turtle, as well as the green
      turtle, Ridley sea turtle, leatherback turtle and loggerhead turtle. Four mammals are considered endangered: the
      Hawaiian hoary bat; the kohola, or humpback whale; the sperm whale; and the endemic Hawaiian monk seal.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Any film featuring Bradley Cooper's gorgeous blue eyes is automatically on my must-see list and they did not
      disappoint in 'The Words,' which is so intense and confusing that I was pretty lost by the end!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      For the first time ever I was taking the family on the road. We stayed with my in-laws, which on life's list of
      experiences ranks right below sitting in a tub full of scissors.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When you are organizing a group of people, the first thing that we do is we talk about the history of what other
      people have been able to accomplish - people that look like them, workers like them, ordinary people, working
      people - and we give them the list: these are people like yourself; this is what they were able to do in their
      community.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      An income tax form is like a laundry list - either way you lose your shirt.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Don't define the game by the list of the features. Define it by the experience you want to have.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If you've got a plan, it's not just like a pipe dream. You have a step-by-step list of things to do to get to your
      goal.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      You've got to be like a fan at your show, just wild out. I make eye contact. I get in the crowd and kick it with
      'em, stage dive, mosh. I make 'em laugh. I go out there and turn up, have fun. There's no set list; I don't have
      rehearsals.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I also pray for favor and His anointing on my life and ministry that I might have spiritual blessing when I
      minister to people. They're my principal prayers; I don't have a prayer list that I go down.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      In addition, we were unable to meet openly to discuss the progress of the book, for we were both on the list of
      persons banned from communicating with other banned persons.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      From Clara Barton's tireless work founding the American Red Cross to the first female Medal of Honor winner, Dr.
      Mary Walker, to our first female combat fighter pilot Lt. Kara Hultgreen, no list of American heroes is complete
      without the names of some of these extraordinary women.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am scared easily, here is a list of my adrenaline - production: 1: small children, 2: policemen, 3: high places,
      4: that my next movie will not be as good as the last one.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When I was going to gay bars in my 20s and 30s, the older guys there explained to me that the police would
      occasionally raid these places and march the clients out, load them onto paddy wagons, drive them down to the
      station, photograph them, fingerprint them and put their names on a list. They were doing nothing wrong, and it
      was criminalized.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The list of gifted teachers and librarians who find their jobs in jeopardy for defending their students' right to
      read, to imagine, to question, grows every year.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The rich are different. Their wants are very high maintenance. They'll pick eye color and hair color, all the way
      down to what she does for a living, what school she went to. Their list can be extremely long. But at the end of
      the day, dating is dating, because they're human beings.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I like the idea of putting your Christmas wish list up and letting people share it.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Elon Musk should be at the top of the list of people to emulate when it comes to leading large organizations that
      are highly maneuverable and use it as a competitive advantage.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One part puzzle mixed with one part racer with just a dash of art and music just to blend everything together,
      'Dyad' takes you on a fast-paced trip down a tunnel filled with lights and a shifting list of rules to keep your
      neurons nimble.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It is unacceptable that disabled veterans in Illinois rank at the bottom of the list when it comes to disability
      pay. We owe our disabled veterans more than speeches, parades and monuments.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I've had all six of my books reach the New York Times bestseller list, which is especially rewarding seeing as I
      flunked out of high school twice because I couldn't write. It just goes to show you that we learn from our
      mistakes.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There are three kinds of people in this world: 1) People who make lists, 2) People who don't make lists, and 3)
      People who carve tiny Nativity scenes out of pecan hulls. I'm sorry, there isn't really a third category; it's
      just that a workable list needs a minimum of three items, I feel.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'd like to one day be featured on a list of inspirational people who have made a difference in the world, whether
      it be helping underprivileged people or putting an end to the poaching of wildlife in Africa.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I don't believe in very many things, but art is definitely one of them. And at the top of that list, film and art
      influence our world's culture much more than many of us understand and fully respect.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>I don't keep a Bucket List. I'm open to anything.</content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Saying you have a political solution is like saying you can write a pop song that's going to stay at the top of
      the list forever. I don't have many illusions about this, but I'm not cynical about it.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I could probably give you a list of a dozen pet peeves I have about my own physicality and why I couldn't get a
      second date.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One of the most effective tools in Brazil's efforts to eradicate slavery is a register compiled by the government
      that lists individuals and businesses found using slave labor. Those on the 'dirty list,' as the register is
      known, are fined and remain on it for a minimum of two years during which they cannot access public funds.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am methodical about my email inbox, and I always have a physical to-do list. Without those two things, I think
      I'd lose my mind.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I realize that every time we discuss a job placement and look at a list of both male and female candidates,
      there's a question that comes up pretty much all the time for the woman: 'Will she know how to assert herself?'
      It's not meant to be malicious. It's more, 'Will she manage to take leadership of the team you want to entrust to
      her?'
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have been given a list of 35 white farmers in Mashonaland West alone. We say no to whites owning our land, and
      they should go... They can own companies and apartments... but not the soil. It is ours, and that message should
      ring loud and clear in Britain and the United States.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Women in particular need to keep an eye on their physical and mental health, because if we're scurrying to and
      from appointments and errands, we don't have a lot of time to take care of ourselves. We need to do a better job
      of putting ourselves higher on our own 'to do' list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      In the old days, you would have one lawyer to handle everything: speeding tickets, buying a house, contracts,
      litigation, real estate, copyrights, leasing, entertainment, intellectual property, forensic accounting, criminal
      offenses... the list goes on. Now, you have to have a separate lawyer for each one of those categories!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      A man's interest in a single bluebird is worth more than a complete but dry list of the fauna and flora of a town.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm just trying to pass Tim Duncan in championships if I can one day. That's my motivation; that's what I strive
      for. Tim is one of the greatest players who has ever played, so if I could get close or reach that plateau and
      have my name on that list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I got a chain letter by fax. It's very simple. You just fax a dollar bill to everybody on the list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Laughter is the best medicine - unless you're diabetic, then insulin comes pretty high on the list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      My first joke that ever aired on 'Late Night' was for a list of 'Top 10 Least Popular Summer Camps.' My
      contribution - 'Camp Tick in beautiful Lyme, Connecticut' - squeaked in at No. 10. Like a trip to Camp Tick, my
      time at 'Late Night' faded into memory like a short session at a dicey summer camp.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One of the things I realized is that if you do not take control over your time and your life, other people will
      gobble it up. If you don't prioritize yourself, you constantly start falling lower and lower on your list, your
      kids fall lower and lower on your list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The problem is, I think, that so many of us pray as if we are ordering groceries. We pick up the telephone and
      say, 'Is this the right place to place my order?' and we proceed right to dictating our order. When we have then
      ended that list, we hang up.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Racism isn't born, folks, it's taught. I have a two-year-old son. You know what he hates? Naps! End of list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Emphasize your strengths on your resume, in your cover letters and in your interviews. It may sound obvious, but
      you'd be surprised how many people simply list everything they've ever done. Convey your passion and link your
      strengths to measurable results. Employers and interviewers love concrete data.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Growing up, I had the weird fantasy list: I wanted to be Alice Cooper, Steven Spielberg, and Stan Lee. You have to
      have almost psychotic drive, because you're going to have years of failure.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have here in my hand a list of two hundred and five people that were known to the Secretary of State as being
      members of the Communist Party and who nevertheless are still working and shaping the policy of the State
      Department.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Kindle Singles is publishing on skates. It prints like lightning; our book meets readers in hours. I've spent so
      many years waiting for publishers to consider whether they wanted to print a book of mine, making contracts,
      taking months to fit it into the Fall list or the Spring list, fitting it into an advertising plan.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It's important to go into the grocery store with a plan and a list. But it's a skeleton - you need to know how to
      deviate from it and adapt it to what ingredients are available and fresh.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Northwestern's alumni list is truly impressive. This university has graduated best-selling authors, Olympians,
      presidential candidates, Grammy winners, Peabody winners, Emmy winners, and that's just me!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Taking care of myself used to be at the bottom of my list, but I'm all about wellness.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The list of erratic actions from Mohammed bin Salman is long: the jailing of royal family members, the detention
      of the Lebanese prime minister, a nonsensical feud with Qatar, the growing internal repression of political
      speech, and the disastrous war in Yemen.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I think the world will just be better if AI is helping us. It will reduce the cost of goods, giving us good
      education, changing the way we run hospitals and the health-care system - there's just a long list of things.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm sure everyone knows now that only a few have performed in Madison Square Garden. That list is so small. Now
      I'm on that list. I'm a part of a very small group, which is unbelievable. You relish in that moment for a second.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I love dress shopping, and I love talking about the wedding food. That's what makes me happy. If you tell me to do
      a guest list, I cry. I hate it.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      No matter what your laundry list of requirements in choosing a mate, there has to be an element of good luck and
      good fortune and good timing.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      No matter what your company does - build, manage, produce, import - as an owner, you can't avoid the hard work and
      skip straight to success. No class can give you that, no YouTube video can teach it, and no book can mark it off
      your list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Scientists use satellites to track weather, map ice sheet melting, detect diseases, show ecosystem change... the
      list goes on and on. I think nearly every scientific field benefits or could benefit from satellite imagery
      analysis.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One of my great regrets, and I don't have many, is that I spent too long putting people's status and reputation
      ahead of their more important qualities. I learned far too late in life that a long list of letters after
      someone's name is no guarantee of compassion, kindness, humour, all the far more relevant stuff.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We saw a need to develop a community for artists to get their music out to the masses. With MySpace, when they
      went out on tour, they could actually tour nationally. The band might have 20,000 friends on their list and send
      out a bulletin saying, 'I'm going to be in Austin on Tuesday night. Come see our show.'
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      NASA has spin-offs, and it's a huge and very impressive list, including accurate and affordable LASIK eye surgery.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      People talk about this 'bucket list': 'I need to go to this country, I need to skydive.' Whereas I need to think
      as much as I can, to feel as much as I can, to be conscious and observe and understand me and the people around me
      as much as I can.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I suggest Substituting Inedible Nurturance, or SIN. Don't replace overeating with virtuous work or exercise;
      instead, make a list of things you love, from watching TV to hanging out with favorite people.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I just think that sometimes we hang onto people or relationships long after they've ceased to be of any use to
      either of you. I'm always meeting new people, and my list of friends seems to change quite a bit.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There's definitely a list of things I'd like to do. But there's been a lot of things I hadn't even thought would
      have been possible to do that I'd been able to do, so I think I'll surprise myself and keep breaking that glass
      ceiling to see what's next. Hopefully people get surprised - that's my main goal.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The world has a shortage of solution providers. Everybody want to be in the 'Forbes' list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I didn't make 'The New York Times' bestseller list until 'Charmed Thirds,' and then again for 'Fourth Comings.' It
      gave me a certain validation, and it certainly helps position me for future books, but it's not something I think
      about on a daily basis.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I would love to be a Bond girl. That is on my bucket list, definitely.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The legal fight over climate change begins in the United States with the Clean Air Act Amendments of 1977. Under
      the Act, the E.P.A. is required to publish a list of 'stationary sources' of air pollution, of which the most
      important are power plants.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Marriage commissioners who choose not to marry homosexuals are being fired. A Knights of Columbus chapter in
      British Columbia is in court because it chooses not allow a lesbian group to use its facility for marriage
      ceremonies. The list goes on.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Every White House has had its intellectuals, but very few presidents have been intellectuals themselves - Thomas
      Jefferson, John Adams, Woodrow Wilson, the list more or less stops there.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Believe me when I say this: you can't please everyone in concert, even though I still want to. Someone always
      wants you to sing a song that isn't necessarily on your set list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When I get up and work out, I'm working out just as much for my girls as I am for me, because I want them to see a
      mother who loves them dearly, who invests in them, but who also invests in herself. It's just as much about
      letting them know as young women that it is okay to put yourself a little higher on your priority list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When struggling to get out of bed in the morning due to pain and exhaustion, the last thing on the priority list
      is going to get a blow dry.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Resume: a written exaggeration of only the good things a person has done in the past, as well as a wish list of
      the qualities a person would like to have.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The list of U.S. vetoes at the Security Council to protect Israeli aggression and occupation is huge.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Talent without effort is wasted talent. And while effort is the one thing you can control in your life, applying
      that effort intelligently is next on the list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Never put your family, friends, or significant other low on your priority list. Prefer a handful of truly close
      friends to a hundred acquaintances.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have a very small list of friends with whom I gel and love to spend my time with.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I haven't got the slightest idea how to change people, but still I keep a long list of prospective candidates just
      in case I should ever figure it out.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have a terrifying long list of fears. Literally everything - diseases, spiders... and people getting tired of
      me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We're all lonely, but I'd rather be lonely by myself than with a long list of duties and obligations. I think
      that's why people kill themselves, really.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Make sure you are safe, and never ever put yourself in a compromising situation, but once that is checked off the
      list, I think it's really important for us to remember that someone needs us, and that your act of
      giving/helping/doing can truly become an act of grace once you get out of your head.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Since I became CEO, 87 percent of the companies in the Fortune 500 are off the list. What that says is that
      companies that don't reinvent themselves will be left behind. I also think that's true of people. And I think it's
      true of countries.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      My favorite books are a constantly changing list, but one favorite has remained constant: the dictionary. Is the
      word I want to use spelled practice or practise? The dictionary knows. The dictionary also slows down my writing
      because it is such interesting reading that I am distracted.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The older you get, the things that you thought you wanted to do when you were younger, you're checking them off
      your list because you no longer want to them.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      A lot of people want to donate a kidney, but they're not in a position to because they have health issues of their
      own, and a lot of people need them. That's why the list is long and it takes a long time.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Training is not quite a thing for me yet. It is definitely on my list of things to do.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Ask any teenage girl to describe her perfect bedroom, and you'll get answers like 'a room with a private phone
      line, a place to hang out with friends, and for it to be way-cool and funky.' Ask parents the same question, and
      'a locked door that opens on their 21st birthday' might top the list!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I like salty, creamy foods. I could sit down with a bag of chips and French onion dip and go to town! That would
      be on my last-supper list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      As a child, recognizing my difference from other kids, I went to the local public library to try to better
      understand my reality. Back then, many library card catalogues didn't even list 'homosexuality' as a topic.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      In all planing you make a list and you set priorities.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Seeing your name on the list for KP or guard duty when you're in the Army is like reading a bad review.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Number one, you can sell before you buy. I call it reverse e-commerce. You take a picture, you list it for sale,
      you sell it, you collect the revenue, then you go buy it and send it to the customer.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      'Rigoletto' has long been one of my favorite operas, and it was on my short list way back when I first talked to
      Peter Gelb. I started thinking about what I could bring to this masterpiece, which has been seen all over the
      world for so many years.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      With my daughter, who at the time was one, my domestic life needed to take more precedent and really with my own
      self I needed to develop quite a bit more. So that put Blur down the list of priorities quite a lot by the time I
      came to thinking about it.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I think I ended up on 'People's '50 Most Beautiful People' list just because of eyeliner, which is kind of a
      bummer. But if you do find the right color, it will make your eyes pop.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Our profession is very much like going to a cocktail party, you check out the guest list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      In my family, we let our boys have a say in what veggie side they want for dinner that night. We list off a
      handful of options and get them excited about helping to plan the dinner menu. They're much more inclined to
      finish their plates when they've helped decide what goes on them.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      All the evidence shows very clearly that if you are a member of a trade union you are likely to get better pay,
      more equal pay, better health and safety, more chance to get training, more chance to have conditions of work that
      help if you have caring responsibilities... the list goes on!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      At any given time I'm listening to the Cory Branan, Leonna Naess, Eve 6, the King's Noyse, Sean Paul, Green Day,
      the BoDeans, Buddy Holly, Nowell Sing We Clear... the list goes on and on. But I rarely listen to music while I
      write. I start typing the lyrics.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      'Losing My Edge' was an anthem for the aging music nerd, with lyrics detailing a comically epic list of historical
      dates, bands and attended gigs: the anti-hipster's defence against 'the art-school Brooklynites in little jackets
      and borrowed nostalgia for the unremembered Eighties.'
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Of all the creatures in the world that really frighten me - the hyena in Africa, the great white shark - leopard
      seals are near the top of the list. They're killers. If my team spots one, they'll pull me out of the water.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>Direction is always on my wish list.</content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I was downright obnoxious. In second grade, we had some program where we kept a public list of all the books we
      read. I think it even included the number of pages. In my nerdy mind, having the longest and most impressive list
      was somehow going to make up for the fact that I couldn't climb a rope or do a backwards summersault in PE.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I find that I do my best work at the beginning of the day, but I'm rarely in a writing mood when I sit down. I'm
      usually somewhat sleep-deprived, and I always have a long list of other responsibilities calling my name.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I believe film and television should reflect our society, and the reality is that there are people in many
      different shapes and sizes, ethnicities, sexual orientation - the list goes on.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The list of my favorite experiences would almost equal the list of plays I've been in. There are a few exceptions,
      but out of politeness I'm not going to mention them. If you don't have a few stinkers, you can't appreciate the
      good ones.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Downloading is definitely on the rise, but not because it's free - that's probably third on the list - but because
      it's immediate and the selection is virtually unlimited.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When you've written 10 books and have six on the New York Times best-seller list - and four have been No. 1 - I
      think you have a right to be a member of Congress.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I contribute a large amount of money to the Southern Poverty Law Center, so I'm on their mailing list for all
      their Klan Watch newsletters. I'm very well aware of White Power movements in America.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am not immune to the lure of a signed record, flier or set list. The fact that your music heroes potentially
      had, in their own hands, the record you now have in yours is kind of cool. When the musician has departed, it can
      give the thing a unique power.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There are certain people that are marked for death. I have my little list of those that treated me unfairly.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I've never been able to say I've been influenced by a list of artists I like because I like thousands and
      thousands and I've been influenced in some way by all of them.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Write your goals down in detail and read your list of goals every day. Some goals may entail a list of shorter
      goals. Losing a lot of weight, for example, should include mini-goals, such as 10-pound milestones. This will keep
      your subconscious mind focused on what you want step by step.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There is, however, another purpose to which academies contribute. When they consist of a limited number of
      persons, eminent for their knowledge, it becomes an object of ambition to be admitted on their list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The object of our prayers should not be to present a wish list or a series of requests but to secure for ourselves
      and for others blessings that God is eager to bestow, according to His will and timing.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Set lists are tough because you come up with this structure of how the songs are going to go from one to the next,
      but at the same time, you have to be spontaneous and take requests and change the set list at the drop of a hat.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Know the official post office abbreviations for all 50 states without having to consult a list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'd split up with a boyfriend and gone to Vermont to stare at my navel, and then 9/11 happened, and I spent days
      being scared of what was happening in the world. So I made a list of all the things I wanted to do, and at the top
      was adopt a baby. Nine months and two days later, I brought my daughter home.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Every New Year comes with a list of predictions. Self-predictions, world predictions, how many times Lindsay Lohan
      will get arrested predictions, etc. I reserve the annual trend for people with genuine psychic ability and/or
      bloggers.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If you asked my kids to describe me, they'd go through a whole list of words before even thinking about
      Parkinson's. And honestly, I don't think about it that much either. I talk about it because it's there, but it's
      not my totality.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am not looking for a life partner right now. But if I've to list out the requirements, I have a huge list. But
      the first requirement is he should be tall and should be taller than me; even I wear heels.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      As your career grows, the list of things that makes you happy should not become smaller, it should become bigger.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Among the hardest-working players I've ever been associated, Yao stands at the very top of the list. Beyond that,
      though, here's what truly separated him from everyone else: His ability to enjoy other people's successes.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      As Lord Chesterfield said of the generals of his day, 'I only hope that when the enemy reads the list of their
      names, he trembles as I do.'
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Something happened when the memoirs of so-called ordinary people, like myself, suddenly hit the bestseller list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The 2013 Boston Marathon was, for me, a milestone. A bucket list event that was supposed to be my last marathon
      until my next big milestone, turning 50. But I couldn't leave marathoning on a memory like that, so I am running
      this year to honor everyone in the running community and those unsung heroes from April 15, 2013.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Make a list of the people in your 'choir'... If you're not on your own list, then you're doing something wrong.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One of the core values of the startup world is that you must have a list of core values. Like all abstract ideas,
      they're easy to dream up and tricky to implement.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If you made a list of reasons why any couple got married, and another list of the reasons for their divorce, you'd
      have a hell of a lot of overlapping.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Those who know me know I'm passionate about lists, and top of my list of priorities is my family. My wife Joan and
      I do not consider our legacy to our children to be wealth or fame but the opportunity to pursue happiness by
      following their own path.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have a long list of how people call me: 'The Prince of Design,' 'Beethoven of Design,' 'the Dutch Prince of
      Design' and the list goes on and on and on... and also the 'Lady Gaga of Design!' I am fine with it. I think she
      is an amazing character who has innovated the music scene and is respected by so many people; she is surprising.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I had an encyclopedia with a list of flags in the back, so I would look at all these flags of China and Liberia
      and England and Denmark and whatever, and I learned all the different flags, and I tried to imagine what it would
      be like to be voyaging on some of these ships.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I loved WWE , but in the end, I was unhappy. It was just like planning an escape from a maximum security prison.
      I'd released a list of potential opponents online, so when the 90-day no-compete clause was up, I had matches
      booked on good faith. I thought about the follow-up.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When 'Twilight' hit the New York Times bestseller list at number 5, for me that was the pinnacle, that was the
      moment. I never thought I would be there. And I keep having moments like that where you just stop and say, wait a
      minute - how is this still going up? I'm waiting for the rug to be pulled out from under me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      You fall in love with somebody who fits within what I call your 'love map,' an unconscious list of traits that you
      build in childhood as you grow up. And I also think that you gravitate to certain people, actually, with somewhat
      complementary brain systems.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      People have this impression that I'm a little kooky, but I'm actually very OCD. I love order and organization. I'm
      a big list maker. But if I cross off too many tasks, and it's hard to see the remaining ones, I have to start a
      new list. Now that's OCD.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Every day I get up and look through the Forbes list of the richest people in America. If I'm not there, I go to
      work.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm not goal-oriented so much as I'm constantly aware of what I'm passionate about, and I'm constantly updating
      the list. I envision many possible futures for myself where I could be happy, so I just try to keep my passions
      alive.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Arranging an official dinner in an embassy is a little like writing a script for a play. The prolog is the guest
      list, often the most difficult part of the whole creative operation.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I put a list together. It was like: Get health insurance, get a car, get a bigger apartment, travel more, get a
      record deal, get a publishing deal, sell 10,000 units, be a part of a No. 1 album, make a million dollars. I got
      to check off 90 percent of the stuff last year. I hit some serious landmarks in 2015.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I tell people: walk around for one month and write down three problems in your life every day. At first it's easy
      - you got stuck in traffic, you missed your alarm - but by the end of the month you're looking really hard to get
      your 90 problems. The most common things on your list are now billion-dollar businesses.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If you tell Canadians that you want to interview them for a critical piece on the Canadian healthcare system,
      they'll put on their best trophy-wife smile for the camera and list its many accolades. Catch them on a day with
      their guard down in need of actual care, however, and the truth comes out.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm vain enough to want do a movie again, but right now more roles are the last thing on my list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      My mom is very structured. She gets up, she does her prayers, and she eats her oatmeal with blueberries and Greek
      yogurt, and she has her prayer list, and she doesn't worry too much about things.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Anyway, several rewrites later, Del Rey Books did publish my first novel, and it did become the first work of
      fiction on the New York Times trade paperback bestseller list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      For everyday diners in Manhattan, cracking the waiting list at Nobu is said to be harder than getting courtside
      tickets for the Knicks.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It's been an incredible experience, playing with Twisted Sister, Stone Sour, Avenged Sevenfold, jamming with Ace
      Frehley and Peter Criss, and the list goes on and on and on.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>We all have that long to-do list.</content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Always have a plan when you shop. Have your list ready so that you know who you're purchasing gifts for and an
      estimate on how much you're going to spend.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It took me a long time to find out that I was born to be an actor. It was the last thing on my list, although my
      list was very small. I didn't know what to do. But kids weren't supposed to know what to do back then; we were all
      cute and we'd find out what we'd do later in life.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      My mom, who's been in the restaurant business for 40 years, is the number-one influence in my life. But I look up
      to a lot of people in the industry. Tops on my list is Mario Batali. My mom and Mario taught me the same lesson:
      Food is love.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      A good way to take a baby step into the world of animal rights is to make a list of small things you can do to
      help your issue and work your way up to the big things. Make a promise to do one thing on your list each month.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Between the kids, the jobs and everything, no matter what color you are, cardio is probably not on the top of your
      list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Not long ago I made a list of Doc Ford books I would like to do, and I came up with 11 pretty easily. I like to
      let the characters go their own ways and see what happens. I find them fascinating.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm as surprised as anybody. I never would have thought I'd be here talking about having a cooking show on the
      Food Network. It wasn't on my list of things, but it's fun, and I'm having a good time.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I don't care about no boxing legacy. I don't care where they put me on the list of all-time greats - let them put
      me at the bottom.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I can go into LinkedIn and search for network engineers and come up with a list of great spear-phishing targets
      because they usually have administrator rights over the network. Then I go onto Twitter or Facebook and trick them
      into doing something, and I have privileged access.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm really annoyed by the wave of country music that's just a list of stuff. It almost sounds like L.A. people
      writing country music, because it's just a list of stuff: 'My pickup truck and my cowboy boots and my Levi's jeans
      and my girlfriend with the short shorts.' It's so boring!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      That's absolutely correct and in addition to that life just isn't an accident of the laws of physics. There's a
      long list of experiments that suggest just the opposite.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      In our early days, being recognized on any list of great companies was hard to imagine. There were times when we
      sold the office furniture to make payroll.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Aerosmith's 'Rocks' is on the list of my top favorite albums of all time.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      As the leader of the most powerful nation in the world, our president is more than a list of policies. They set
      the tone of our national character.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Don't add people to your subscriber list just because they once wrote you a note. Or once answered a note you
      wrote to them. Don't put your address book into your newsletter database. Let your readers sign up.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Here is just the beginning of a list of skills that exam results cannot possibly hope to reflect: interpersonal
      skills, the ability to entertain, how articulate we are as speakers, our ability to work as part of a team, the
      ability to deal with challenges and invention.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am very harsh on myself. I can point out a list. My nose is very strange. I have a very round face. I sound so
      ungrateful. Obviously I'm being hard on myself. Whether it's body dysmorphia, or whatever it is, I can always find
      something wrong.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I liked to scrapbook and collage a whole lot in high school. I'm always ripping things out of magazines, and
      always collecting quotes from the Internet. When I was 17, I loved AIM. I was obsessed with my buddy list!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We recognize the significant burden on patients from continued, rising insurance premiums and being forced
      increasingly to pay the full list price for medicines at the pharmacy counter.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have a number of places on my wish list, including Antarctica, the Norwegian fjords, and the Amazon. I have a
      passion for wilderness, and Siberia is on my list - however, that may be a bridge too far.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Girls are sitting around talking about boys, right? Or complaining about boys, when they have their heart broken
      or whatever, and they need music for that, right? And they need music for that. So it's hard to find the right
      music. Not everyone has the right list or knows a DJ.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Every woman is sexy in her own way. It is up to men to step up and make women feel like they are No. 1 on that
      list. There is no such thing as perfection.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      In the movies, every crazy old fart needs a cool old car. Jack Nicholson drove a spiffy yellow 1970 Dodge
      Challenger two-door in 'The Bucket List.' In 'Gran Torino,' the cranky pensioner played by Clint Eastwood not only
      owned a 1972 GT Sport, he also used to build cars like that at the Ford plant.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When the economy is strong, people tend to buy three things from the top of their wish list. But when things are
      bad, people often buy only the first thing on their list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Reversal of ageing is high on my list of things to do, and not just because I'm getting old.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If I see myself on a worst-dressed list - and I've been on many of them - I tend to have low self esteem for 24
      hours. I just like to feel comfortable, and I like being excited about whatever it is I'm wearing. I hate
      subjecting myself to that kind of criticism!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Once you've published a few books, you drag around this ball and chain of a back list. All the evidence of how few
      you've sold is there. I think a lot of writers my age have this strange experience of going from would-be to
      has-been.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We survived for hundreds of years under the old banking structure. You'd have clearing banks, then merchant banks
      doing the racy stuff, and then building societies where you'd join a waiting list for a mortgage. But then banks
      started buying stockbrokers, doing mortgages, and you ended up with these big banking groups doing everything.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There's a long list of technologies that have now made it possible to carry out very precise search efforts in the
      deep sea.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am sometimes asked to name my favourite books. The list changes, depending on my mood, the year, tricks played
      by memory. I might mention novels by Nabokov and Calvino and Tolkien on one occasion, by Fitzgerald and Baldwin
      and E.B. White on another. Camus often features, as do Tolstoy, Borges, Morrison and Manto.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We invite American companies looking to raise capital to list on the Bahrain Stock Exchange. The region has a
      liquidity oversupply approximating $1 trillion and this pool of capital can be tapped into by creative American
      companies. The next Facebook may very well get funded on the BSE.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      This isn't about grabbing people's guns; this isn't about changing the Second Amendment. This simply says that
      someone who is on the terrorist watch list - a dangerous terrorist - should not be able to purchase a gun.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When people learn that I'm a qualified primary school teacher, I'm often met with surprise and a list of
      questions, including, 'How do the children react? How do you do it?' Children are some of the most open and
      inclusive individuals. It's often us adults who have difficulties in accepting difference.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The Victorian language of flowers began with the publication of 'Le Language des Fleurs,' written by Charlotte de
      Latour and printed in Paris in 1819. To create the book - which was a list of flowers and their meanings - de
      Latour gathered references to flower symbolism throughout poetry, ancient mythology, and even medicine.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have traveled down this path before - 'List of Seven' and 'Twin Peaks' both have thematic similarities - but
      'Paladin' took me much deeper into the intuitive underground. Always bearing in mind Joseph Campbell's Rule No. 1:
      When entering a labyrinth, don't forget your ball of twine.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It's always on everyone's list, like, 'What's New Orleans like?' I think people have a pre-conceived idea, like
      it's just Mardi Gras and Bourbon Street. But really, there's so much culture, the music's great, the food's great.
      It's not good for the waistline! But I'm actually from the South, I'm from Georgia, so the weather doesn't bother
      me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I don't storyboard, and I don't really shot list. I let the shots be determined by how the actors and I figure out
      the blocking in a scene, and then from there, we cover it.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We are a nation built on principles of freedom, and high on the list of freedoms is freedom of religious
      expression.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      You can't predict the future, and you've got to go with your gut on these things, and I'm sure if you speak to a
      laundry list of CEOs and people who have gone through the startup process themselves, they'll say it's an endless
      hurdle race, and you are inevitably going to catch your legs on hurdles, and it's just how you roll with that.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The biggest potential of Facebook is that people can build networks. For business persons, it means that they can
      build their list of leads, which they can look upon as prospects for furthering their business.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      For the longest time, I was always like a guy that people would think they went to high school with. They'd be
      like, 'How do I know you?' After, we'd play a guessing game. I'd say, 'I'm an actor,' and they'd go, 'Oh, what
      have you been in?' I'd list my credits, and they wouldn't really remember me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The reason I wrote 'Hit List' is the 50 mysterious deaths of witnesses to the JFK assassination. We're talking
      about CIA agents, FBI agents, reporters, people who had foreknowledge, or people who spoke too much afterward.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm not invited. I'm not on the A list, haven't been on it in 20 years and my feet have never trod its red fluffy
      carpets.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If I can hit No. 1 on the 'New York Times' best-seller list, I'm thinking of having the entire list tattooed on my
      body somewhere. It would be fabulous.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If you don't make the best-seller list, if you don't get shortlisted for any prizes, it's goodbye.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I looked back at the years since I'd left college and thought of the list of things I'd have liked to do. I'd
      always wanted to write a book - not a small undertaking. I never felt I had the time or creative energy to spare
      in order to write one as well as I wanted.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      What gets left out is the narrative between the bullets, which would tell us who's going to do what and how we're
      going to achieve the generic goals on the list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There are a few things for the New York actor that you hope to one day cross off the bucket list. One of them was
      I got to do an episode of 'Blue Bloods,' which was really fun.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>Being cool is not exactly at the top of my list.</content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When you start a new job or a particular journey, you really don't know what to expect. I mean, you hear about
      your name being on the bestsellers list, but it doesn't really mean anything. Like, really, what does that
      translate to?
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The standard way to record a meeting is to list people's names, the topics, and action items. The visual way is to
      doodle a rectangle (the table) populated by figures (the participants) sitting around the table with their
      comments as cartoon word balloons.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      To be No. 1 on the 'New York Times' best-seller list, well, that's alarming. Having been a stand-up comedian, I
      think it's surprising to a lot of people that I had the insight I had.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Listen, here's the thing about an English degree - if you sat somebody down and asked them to make a list of the
      writers they admire over the last hundred years, see how many of them got a degree in English.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Why can't somebody give us a list of things that everybody thinks and nobody says, and another list of things that
      everybody says and nobody thinks?
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      People across metro Detroit face discrimination every day in housing, employment, insurance - the list goes on. It
      might not always be explicit and in your face, but my residents know when they're being mistreated.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I wish I could do a lot of things different. I'm not going to tell you what they are, but if I had a list of all
      my films right now, I'd go, 'Okay, I'll cross that one out and cross that one out and cross that one out and cross
      that one out.' Really. But I've made over 40 films. How can I not have some losers in there?
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One thing that I get from a lot of people with 'American Gods' is people saying that they would love some kind of
      glossary with a list of all the Gods and who they are, so that they can look them up.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm going to win so much money this year, my caddie will make the top twenty money winner's list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Black people have been qualified to be president for hundreds of years. George Washington Carver could have been
      president. I could go on with a list of black men that were qualified to be the president of the United States. So
      the Obama victory is progress for white people.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm addicted to working. I mean, I have a list of 100 countries I want to play in. I'm basically killing myself by
      travelling so much, for no reason whatsoever.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      A deadly sins addendum is long overdue. Life has changed since Pope Gregory the Great scribbled his initial list
      in the sixth century.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There are plenty of problems in the world, and doubtless climate change - or whatever the currently voguish phrase
      for it all is - certainly is one of them. But it's low on my list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      My mom and I had the same vision, and we want the same things. We would always make a goal list every year.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It's sad that grandkids show up at the end of obituaries, way behind the list of work place achievements, social
      clubs and survivors. Why last? If you've got grandkids, you know they're first when it comes to the joy in your
      life.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When I was 50 years old, I actually decided to draw up a list of half a dozen things that I really hadn't done
      very well, and I was going to make efforts to improve. One of them was skiing, and I really did become a very much
      better skier.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I've never followed a list in my life, and that's probably what has created so much nervous energy in my body.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I know that every time I list something that I am, I am potentially alienating a whole group of people. Publicists
      and managers will encourage you not to say what political party you belong to, what you eat, what you don't eat,
      who you sleep with and all that stuff.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I always liked film as a teaching tool - a way of getting exposed to ideas that had never been presented to me. It
      just wasn't on the list of career options where I grew up.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I was the kid who never won the races. I never jumped the highest. I wasn't on the list of the high-achieving.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I was the kid who never won the races... I wasn't on the list of the high-achieving.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I would say there are some foods that I strongly recommend that you do not eat. No. 1 on that list, I believe, is
      doughnuts. Comfort food. Zero value. Don't eat them.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      One of the best mental disciplines for people to implement is simply putting together a schedule or a task list
      and actually executing it. Write the list or the schedule the night before, and then do what you said you would
      do. Life becomes much better when you do that.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have a to-do list and I have a farm I care for, and things I like to do for fun - going to movies and all that
      stuff. It's a painfully normal life!
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm wearing a garbage bag. I was put on my own worst-dressed list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I would not advise people to buy a car or house without making a list. You will probably improve your intuitions
      by making a list and then sleeping on it.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      As far back as I can remember, I had an interest in fashion. I used to go to sleepaway camp, and they'd provide a
      list of things that you had to bring, and I always wanted to be a bit more creative than the list allowed. Like,
      if they required chinos, I wanted to hand-paint them.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Bookstore operators tell us that the books which head the bestseller list are books on peace and happiness.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Each night before I go to bed, I take out a small card and write a list of the things I need to do the next day in
      order of their priority.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Like, I took no poetic license with 'Schindler's List' because that was historical, factual documents.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      There's nothing self-serving about what motivated me to bring 'Schindler's List' to the screen.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I could give you a long list of things I like about Britain, but essentially what it comes down to is that I feel
      about Britain the same way I feel about my wife. I'm crazy about my wife - we just kind of suit each other. I
      wouldn't say that she's the most fantastic human being that's ever lived, but she is for me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I know a lot of people who really aren't beautiful because their attitudes are very nasty... Whether I make the 50
      most beautiful list or not, I'm always going to feel like I'm number one most beautiful to myself... I get that
      from my mom, and my daddy and my friends who raised me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It seems every morning I wake up to face a list of 20 things to do, with time only to do 10, and somehow I always
      wind up squishing in 30.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I'm a parent, and I try to take care of my health and keep my life in order. In the last few years I've really had
      to decide what's important to me, and it seems to me that my family and my health are top on the list. And those
      have nothing to do with show business.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      We have a number of difficulties facing our nation, but I believe fatherlessness is right at the top of the list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Every era has its own list of ingredients that are considered exotic and then, 15 years later, they're not.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I've been asked over the years to compile a list of desert-island discs. I couldn't do that. If I was trapped on a
      desert island, I don't think I'd want 10 songs to bring with me.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      As women, we're nurturers by nature. We want to make sure everyone is happy. That's a good thing, but we also have
      to put ourselves on that happiness list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Don't fall into the trap of putting yourself last on the list or not even putting yourself on the list. That's not
      balance; it's not even healthy.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      When you're a father in a marriage, you sort of become the mother's assistant. And you sort of get a list from her
      every day and you run down the list and it feels very much like a chore.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I am a massive bargain hunter, so my list of bargains goes on and on and on.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I think extreme secrecy is a bad sign in all startups. Very few startups die because they tell you exactly how
      their technology works. On the long list of startup killers, that's pretty far down. Though on the list of
      entrepreneur fears, it's pretty high.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The list of what I want to do is so long, I would need a few lifetimes to achieve them. For instance, I would like
      to fly small planes, maybe over the Ganges one day.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      The 'Phoenix Sun' did a list of the unsexiest men in the world, and I made it to number one. I beat out Bin Laden.
      He's a terrorist, hasn't bathed in months. I beat him out. To me it was a great honor.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      My to-do list is so long that it doesn't have an end; it has an event horizon.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I've got a long list of books I wish I'd never written-and I've kept them all out of print for the past 20 years.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I want to be a dad. That's floating to the top of my list. I think it's such an important thing. I'm at the age
      where everyone has kids, and I ask them, 'Is it like a puppy?' And they go, 'It's 10 times a puppy.'
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      If I need a pick-me-up, I pull up a memo file on my phone and type in three things I'm grateful for. The things
      I've typed on other days are still there. It's a long list. Always helps.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I have two young children, and they both adore books. Reading together at bedtime is one of our favorite nightly
      rituals. 'Goodnight, Goodnight Construction Site' by Sherri Duskey Rinker, 'The Giving Tree' by Shel Silverstein,
      and 'On The Night You Were Born' by Nancy Tillman are always on our list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Joe Arpaio needs no help from me getting attention. For years he has been a beacon of bigotry and intolerance for
      all the world to see. The list of human and civil-rights abuses he's committed in Maricopa County is long and well
      documented.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      You can go down the list of great artists and kind of understand that they are products of their environment.
      Whether it's U2 or Henry Rollins or myself or Johnny Lydon, they're gonna be products of their environment.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      With the discovery of the Higgs boson, one of the questions has been ticked off the list, but there are many
      others. We hope that we can find answers or hints for answers to at least some of them. But of course, this is in
      the hands of nature.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I've ended up on some website list or some other list for super right-wing people. They've been tweeting some
      pretty rude stuff at me, so I think there's a sect of America out there that doesn't like certain opinions and can
      really take their claws out when they don't like what you're saying.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      From an app point of view, if you looked at innovation on the PC, you'd be hard pressed to find companies
      innovating. The list is small.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Did I really want to teach my children that a list of successes is the most valuable legacy to leave behind? I
      absolutely did not.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      I don't think Hollywood knows what to do with me. I would imagine that when it comes to romantic comedies, my name
      would be pretty low down on the list.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Make a careful list of all things done to you that you abhorred. Don't do them to others, ever.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      Make another list of things done for you that you loved. Do them for others, always.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      It's fun to write your set list 20 minutes before and keep the crew very much on their toes.
    </content>
  </quote>
  <quote>
    <content>
      From Drew Barrymore to Robert Downey Jr., there's a long list of people who have faced their troubles, wildly
      overcome them, and succeeded.
    </content>
  </quote>
</root>
